Mahmut Taskiran

Android & Cross Mobile Application Developer

Github: github.com/mahmuttaskiran | LinkedIn: linkedIn.com/in/mahmutaskiran | Personal website: mamudo.com
Phone number: +90 546 227 2550 | Email: taskiranmahmutt@gmail.com | Date of birth: 12.02.1994
Place of birth: Adiyaman; Turkey | Martial status: Single

SUMMARY

I am a professional programmer specialized in mobile applications and tools. I have been developing Android native applications with Java and Kotlin, and cross-platform applications with Flutter and React-Native. I have experience developing social media applications (with React-Native and Flutter), IoT applications (with Flutter and Java), sensor-based applications (with Java), WebRTC based applications (with React-Native).

I have been focused on developing my programming skills rather than learning a new programming language. Because I believe that programming is a thinking art, so if I improve my programming knowledge then I can think better.

CORE COMPETENCIES

Java, Kotlin, Android SDK, Flutter, React-Native, Git, Go, Rust and JavaScript.

EXPERIENCES

ARGELOJI, Istanbul Turkey - Mobile Application Developer June 2019 - July 2020

I have been developed BlueOperation's mobile application for Argeloji. BlueOperation offers RTLS solutions that can actively monitor the location of assets to optimize searching time in a wide range of area facilities such as Airports.

argeloji.com

blueoperation.io

play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.blueoperation mobile

POLYINGO (Mobile Application) - Full Stack Mobile Application Developer

May 2019 - Oct 2020

Polyingo is a mobile application that its users can improve their vocabulary and improve their pronunciation by sharing videos about English words and sentences or watching videos shared by other people.

play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.polyingopolyingo.com

CEKIRDEK BILGISAYAR, Istanbul Turkey - Mobile Application Developer

July 2017 - May 2018

I developed a mobile application with Java and Kotlin. It is a business opportunity that I met with cross platform application development by developing a social media application with React-Native.

cekirdekbilgisayar.com.tr

OPCON (Mobile Application) - Full Stack Mobile Application Developer

Apr 2016 - Oct 2017

Opcon is a mobile application that its users can create profiles and messaging their contact. But it offers more than a standard messaging application, the difference between Opcon and other messaging application is that Opcon let its users manage their phones by sending notifier to each other.

github.com/mahmuttaskiran/Opcon

EDUCATION

2012-2016 Bachelor's Degree | Ege University | Radio Television and Cinema 2017-2019 Associate Degree | Anadolu University | Web Design and Programming 2020-2024 Bachelor's Degree | Anadolu University | Information Management Systems

LANGUAGES

Turkish (Native), English (Professional)